<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on CREATIVE LANE</title>
    <link>https://creativelane.me/page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on CREATIVE LANE</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2016 10:52:22 +1100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://creativelane.me/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Intro</title>
      <link>https://creativelane.me/cover-letter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://creativelane.me/cover-letter/</guid>
      <description>Hi EZARD. And welcome to CREATIVE LANE. This dedicated-website job application morphed from idea to delivery in less than a day. I saw your Marketing Coordinator job advertised on SEEK yesterday and I decided to build this for you overnight to showcase me and to tick most of your key selection criteria in the process; demonstrating in real life and real time&amp;hellip;
 I&amp;rsquo;m organised, comprehensive, and proactive I have high attention to detail (in all I do; for me &amp;amp; you) My advanced website skills and knowledge (including website maintenance, management, coding, optimisations, cost minimisations, &amp;amp; more) My photo and photo-editing skills Timely, friendly, professional, proactive, effective communication My passion for creativity and authenticity</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Table of Contents</title>
      <link>https://creativelane.me/contents/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://creativelane.me/contents/</guid>
      <description> About Me I Write, Create, and Conceptualise I Code, Analyse, Optimise, Minimise, and Maximise I Push, Practice, and Exercise I Photograph too BLURBSMITH CONCISELY Referees Reviews Contact Me  Homepage Cover Letter Table of Contents  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://creativelane.me/about-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://creativelane.me/about-me/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m a haloumi whore and affogato addict who dreams of liberation and llama farming. I’ll love you forever if you’ll just read me aloud DFW’s Infinite Jest… a book I’ve owned forever but never read. If you’re not down for David can we fly to Tokyo, suck down saké, and sing karaoke until sunrise? Music and art are the way to my heart when cheese and coffee aren&amp;rsquo;t appropriate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Write, Create, and Conceptualise</title>
      <link>https://creativelane.me/i-write-create-and-conceptualise/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://creativelane.me/i-write-create-and-conceptualise/</guid>
      <description>I’m a brilliant writer, creator, and conceptualist. I&amp;rsquo;m totally biased too&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Code, Optimise, Analyse, Minimise, and Maximise</title>
      <link>https://creativelane.me/i-code-optimise-analyse-minimise-and-maximise/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://creativelane.me/i-code-optimise-analyse-minimise-and-maximise/</guid>
      <description>Writing&amp;rsquo;s my greatest love but not my only skill — I have a bunch of others that gift me great insight into much bigger brand and business puzzles. Such skills allow me to see how different pieces compliment each other, and why, sometimes, compromises must be made.

I Code
I hand-built this website using some of the best tools in the business, including&amp;hellip;
 CloudFlare: Power, protection, and encryption. For free.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Push, Practise, and Exercise</title>
      <link>https://creativelane.me/i-push-practise-and-exercise/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://creativelane.me/i-push-practise-and-exercise/</guid>
      <description>I love to run and strum (the ukulele). They&amp;rsquo;re both new loves in my life and I can&amp;rsquo;t get enough of them. I&amp;rsquo;ve always found physical challenge as rewarding as the creative kind and pushing my mind and body ultimately brings out the best in both. I&amp;rsquo;m grateful to be happy, healthy, and humble and being mindful, minimal, and meanginful plays a large role in my life too. I run regularly, drink rarely, drug never, fast intermittently, and Wim Hof daily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photography</title>
      <link>https://creativelane.me/photography/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://creativelane.me/photography/</guid>
      <description>I love photography. PHACES (www.phac.es) is a personal project of mine where the focus appears to be on those in front of the lens while the real focus is always behind it&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BLURBMSITH</title>
      <link>https://creativelane.me/blurbsmith/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://creativelane.me/blurbsmith/</guid>
      <description>A Blurbsmith paints a thousand words in only nine. —BLURBSMITH
 
BLURBSMITH is a moniker of mine I used to persue visual creative endevours. Below are some of my samples. All concepts and copy [writing] are 100% mine (most photos are stock).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CONCISELY</title>
      <link>https://creativelane.me/concisely/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://creativelane.me/concisely/</guid>
      <description>#WordsWithin is a series I&amp;rsquo;m sending out to the social medias via CONCISELY (my creative writing moniker).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Referees</title>
      <link>https://creativelane.me/referees/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://creativelane.me/referees/</guid>
      <description>Referees? Yes please!

Jay Stockwell
Head of Marketing, Nimble
https://au.linkedin.com/in/jaystockwell
jstockwell@nimble.com.au
0400 400 740

Danielle Duell
CEO, People with Purpose
https://au.linkedin.com/in/danielleduell
danielle@peoplewithpurpose.com.au
0414 949 556
 **Anna Clothier**
National Event Manager, **FILA Australia**
https://au.linkedin.com/in/anna-clothier-30559b28
anna.clothier@fila.com.au
0418 584 098
**Spyro Kalos**
Manager, **AMTA** (Australian Mobile Telecommunications Association)
https://au.linkedin.com/in/spyro-kalos-46596516
spyro.kalos@amta.org.au
0404 015 533 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CREATIVE LANE Reviews</title>
      <link>https://creativelane.me/reviews/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2016 10:52:22 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://creativelane.me/reviews/</guid>
      <description>What an awesome application. I&amp;rsquo;d hire you without even interviewing you.
 — Jay Stockwell. Head of Marketing, NIMBLE (finance)

 I loved CREATIVE LANE; you&amp;rsquo;re such an unique talent. Would you move to Brisbane for the right role?
 — Danielle Duell. CEO, PEOPLE WITH PURPOSE

 Have they hired you yet? You&amp;rsquo;re definitely the best person for the job.
 — My Mum. (Who&amp;rsquo;s never seen this website)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The End</title>
      <link>https://creativelane.me/contact-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://creativelane.me/contact-me/</guid>
      <description>Thanks for reading CREATIVE LANE. This was an ambitious 24 hour challenge to showcase me to you, and because I can&amp;rsquo;t help myself too. I am a real creative and I really create. I hope to hear from you&amp;hellip; Always,
Lane 0488 48 24 24 &amp;middot; lane@alwayslane.com &amp;middot; @THINKLANE </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>